{
  "chapter": 17,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Information privacy is actually a part of information security.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True",
        "False",
        "Depends on situation",
        "Both of them are same"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Generally, to store consumers’ data in encrypted form in the cloud means to preserve information",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Privacy",
        "Both security and privacy",
        "None"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following causes challenge to privacy protection in cloud computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lack of awareness",
        "Weak security implementation",
        "Different legal systems",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "There can be strong security in a system without any privacy.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the compliance maintenance task is cloud service provider’s responsibility alone?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Yes",
        "No. Clients should also be alerted on this."
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "IT auditing is done to check the",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Compliance issues",
        "Security issues",
        "Financial issues",
        "Both a and b"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The IT audit report that is of more value for the cloud consumers is the",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "System audit",
        "Internal audit",
        "External audit",
        "Privacy audit"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Internal audit for compliance is done by service providers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To gain confidence of shareholders",
        "To gain confidence of consumers",
        "To earn more revenue",
        "To improve privacy of the system"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "‘R’ in the term GRC represents",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reliability",
        "Responsiveness",
        "Risk",
        "Recovery"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Privacy in information system is to maintain the secrecy of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stored data of clients",
        "PII of clients",
        "Financial information of clients",
        "Name of clients"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    }
  ]
}
